■
本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 翻译制作
更多美剧更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
《反恐24小时》前情提要
Previously on 24
伯内特先生  你是个卖国贼  恐怖分子
Mr. burnett you are a traitor and a terrorist.
目标在哪儿
Where's the target?
把鲍尔先生带走  他被捕了
Take mr. bauer away. he's under arrest.
有没有任何袭击的消息
Have you learned anything else about the attack?
蕾妮·沃克独自追踪线索
Renee walker followed a lead on her own.
发现了一支以朱玛为首的
Got a visual on a heavily armed commando unit
全副武装的突击队
Lead by juma himself.
比尔·布坎南
Bill buchanan.
蕾妮  沃克说袭击目标是白宫
Renee walker says the target is the white house.
红色警戒  保护总统
Condition red. Secure the president.
没有安全的出口了
There's no safe path out.
我们必须把她送到一层的安全屋
Weeed to secure her in the first floor lockdown.
人质救援小组已各就各位
Hostage rescue teams are moving into place.
他们已经整装待发
They'll be prepared to storm the building
只要一声令下他们就猛攻进去
As soon as the order's given.
副总统阁下
Mr. vice president, terrorists are
恐怖分子控制了白宫
in control of the white houese
除非你能提供里边更多的情况
Until you can provide me more intel on what's going on in there,
否则你决不能轻举妄动
You are instructed to refrain from launching any action.
泰勒总统躲进了安全屋
President taylor is locked in the safe room.
我可以为你做些什么
What is it i can do for you?
请你再帮我找一个进去的方法
I need you to find me another way in.
我在看白宫的人员清单
Well, i'm looking at the white house manifest,
上面说 奥利维亚·泰勒
And according to this, olivia taylor
现在正在你那边
Is presently in the building with you.
把她找出来  你就可以威胁总统开门了
You find olivia taylor, and you'll get the president To open that door.
泰勒总统
President Tayor.
上帝啊 不要
God, no.
如果你不乖乖开门
...if you don't open the door,
我会把你女儿的眼珠
I'm going to cut out your daughter's eyes
一个一个挖出来
One by one.
开门
Open the door.
-总统阁下  -别说了  开门
- Madam president... - no, open the door.
-开门  -我办不到
- open the door. - I can’t.
你有孩子吗  杰克
Do you have children, Jack?
我有个女儿
I have a daughter.
换了你能做到这样吗
Could you do what you're asking me to do?
站在这坐以待毙  眼睁睁看着她任人宰割
Just stand by and watch her butchered?
不能  阁下  但我不是美国总统
No, ma'am, but i am not the president of the united states.
我是总统  我命令你打开门
Well, i am the president, and i am ordering you to open that door.
好了  将军
All right, general,
你抓到我了
You've got me now.
没必要再扣留他们
There's no reason to hold anyone else.
放了他们
Let them go.
以下事件发生于晚上8点到9点
The following takes place between 8 p.m. and 9 p.m.
我们现在所了解到的情况是
Now, what we do know is that the president
恐怖分子展开袭击时总统正在白宫内
Was in the building when the attack took place,
她有可能和其他多数白宫工作人员
And she may have been taken hostage
一同被劫为人质
Along with numerous other white house personnel.
副总统黑沃斯当时不在白宫内
Vice president hayworth was not in the building,
据悉他已被转移到安全地带
And we're told he was moved to a secure location.
联邦调查局已设置了九重警戒线
The fbi has cordoned off a nine-block perimeter
副总统阁下
Mr vice president
是莫斯探员
That was agent moss.
他怎么说
What does he have to say?
他仍然请求您下令实施营救行动
He's still requesting that you authorize a rescue operation.
他有没有进一步关于里面情况的情报
Does he have any more intel About what the hell's going on in there?
没有  他布署了两个小组
No, sir. he deployed two units
使用深层抛物转向探测装置
With deep-band parabolics,
但是设备受到静电干扰
but all they were able get static.
他们认为朱玛正使用某种干扰设备
They think juma's using some kind of jamming equipment.
我们在白宫周围每个可以监测到的角度
They've also got spotters at every
也都安排有监控器
possible angle around the building
但仍然看不到里边的情况
But they haven't been able to see inside.
那我们还是搞不清朱玛是否抓到了总统
We still don't know whether juma has the president,
或者总统是否还躲在安全屋里
Or whether the president is lked inside the safe room?
是的  目前还不清楚
No, sir, we don't.
在我了解总统的处境之前
I will not authorize any action
不会下任何行动指令
Until i know the status of the president.
就这么回复莫斯探员
Relay that to agent moss.
是的  阁下
Yes, sir.
妈妈  我知道我伤透了您的心
Mom, i know that i hurt you.
对不起  是我拒您于千里之外
I'm so sorry for cutting you out of my life.
-没关系  -不  不对
- It's okay - no, it isn't.
您把我从竞选里开除是对的
You were right to fire me off the campaign.
我当时觉得您抛弃了我  所以一直不理您
I felt so betrayed, i turned my back on you.
奥利维亚  别再想这些了
Olivia, don't worry about it.
现在想想  当时太傻了
It all seems so stupid now.
希望您能原谅我
I hope you can forgive me.
亲爱的  我早就原谅你了
Darling, i forgave you a long time ago.
利维  听我说
Livy, you have to listen to me.
我们不会有事的
We really are going to be okay.
你只需睁大眼睛时刻准备好
Just keep your eyes open and be ready.
阿博
Abo.
-不  不  -起来
- No, no. - get up.
别碰她
Leave her alone!
-离她远点儿  -回去
- Get away from her! - get back!
别碰她  求你了
I said leave her alone! please!
奥利维亚  没事的  亲爱的
Olivia, it's okay, darling. it's okay!
比尔  我们得有所行动了
Bill, we need to move
把总统救出来
To try to save the president.
怎么干
How?
在安全屋里
In the lockdown room,
有5瓶CH-4虑毒罐
There were five canisters of ch-4.
咱们向朱玛投降之前 我把瓶口打开
Before we surrendered ourselves over to juma, i open the mouth
五分钟之内
Within the next few minutes,
那个房间会充满天然气
That room is going to be saturated with natural gas.
有一点火花就会爆炸
It's going to take one spark to set it off.
爆炸足够干掉大多数朱玛的手下
I think the explosion is going to be large enough to take out most of juma's men.
那时候你就行动
That's when you can make your move
怎么引爆
How do we set it off?
我跑到安全屋那儿
I'll make a run for the lockdown room.
引开他们的火力
Try and draw their fire.
只要一个流弹就够了
All we need is one stray bullet.
那等于自杀  杰克
That's a suicide play, jack.
没得选了
We don't have a choice.
只要确保你能救出总统
Just make sure you can get to the president
带她从这儿逃出去
And get her out of here.
她知道这个计划  并时刻准备着
She knows about the plan; she'll be ready.
你们在搞什么阴谋诡计
What are you planning?
是不是要行动了
Are you going to do something?
等我们行动时你就知道了  参议员
When it happens, you'll know about it, senator.
妈的  我要知道你们
Damn it, if you're planning something,
-到底在搞什么鬼  -闭嘴吧  参议员
- I want to know what it is. - senator, shut up.
读这份声明
Read this statement.
这是你对在我们的国家犯下的罪行
It is a confession of your crimes
所做的忏悔
Against my country.
你的残暴不仁  将被公诸于众
The atrocities that you have committed will now be seen by the whole world.
我会宣读你的声明的  将军
I'll read your statement, general,
但是我要你释放其他人质
But i need you to release the other hostages.
你已经得偿所愿了
You got what you came for.
你抓到了美国总统
You have the president of the united states.
为了表示诚信
As a sign of good faith...
我会释放一名人质
I will release one of the hostages.
你
You...
站起来
Stand up.
还想让我释放人质吗  泰勒总统
Do you want me to release any hostages,president taylor?
你个王八蛋
You son of a bitch.
要么你乖乖地宣读这份声明
You will read this statement
要么我把所有人都宰了
Or i will do the same thing to everyone here...
先拿你女儿开刀
Starting with your daughter.
将军  上传线路已经设置好了
General, the uplink is complete.
好
All right.
全世界都在翘首以盼了  总统阁下
The world is waiting, Madam president.
我是美国总统
"This is president of the united states.
6小时前  我在没有任何原因
"six hours ago, I ordered our armed forces
与预警的情况下  下令入侵了桑加拉
"to invade sangala without warning and without provocation.
这是一次侵略行为  是犯罪
"this attack was a criminal act motivated solely
是美国为达到滥用其强权和影响力的私欲
"by America's desire to exert its power and influence.
你能禁播这个视频的吧
Tell me you're shutting this down.
做不到  阁下
we can't, sir.
这是直接实况传输到网络上的
It's a live feed straight to the internet.
我才不管那么多  把它给我禁播了
I don't care. shut it down.
它经由多个服务器传输   阁下
It's going out on multiple servers, sir.
光追踪这些服务器就得花上好几个小时
It would take hours just to trace them.
我是德里克·瓦茨
This is derek watts.
稍等
Hold on.
阁下  莫斯探员在视频会议上
Sir, it's agent  moss on teleconference.
接过来
Put him on.
阁下  你也看到那个视频了吧
Sir, are you getting this?
是的  全世界都看到了
Yes. so is the rest of the damn world.
副总统阁下  我相信朱玛来这里
Mr. vice president, i believe juma came here
是为了羞辱并在世人面前处决总统
To humiliate the president and stage a public execution.
营救行动已经准备好
We have a rescue operation in place.
就等您一声令下了
All we need is your authorization.
你根本就不知道朱玛究竟意欲何为
You don't know what juma's intentions are.
这可能只是他今后一系列条件的前奏
This could be a prelude to a set of demands.
他根本就不是来谈条件的  阁下
There are no demands here, sir.
他就是为了以牙还牙
This is about revenge.
朱玛知道他不可能活着走出白宫
Juma knows he'll never get out of the white house alive.
这只是你的推测  莫斯探员
You're speculating, agent moss.
我的顾问认为  最谨慎的做法
My advisor are telling me the most prudent course of action
就是和朱玛谈判
Is to try to initiate communication with juma.
我们已经试过了  他没有回应
We've been trying to do that. he hasn't responded.
阁下  朱玛根本没有谈判的打算
Sir, juma has no desire to negotiate anything.
他只图杀总统而后快
Hes going to kill the president.
阁下  我们的战术计划已经到位
Sir, we have a tactical plan in place.
我们会兵分两路
It's a two-pronged assault, and we're
肯定会杀朱玛一个措手不及
confident that it stands a good chance of catching juma off guard,
但时间不等人  现在必须开始行动
but we're losing time. We have to initiate now.
我不能授权可能会危及到
I cann authorize any action
总统生命的任何行动
At might result in the president's death.
继续想办法和朱玛对话
Keep trying to open dialogue with juma.
在他变卦前不许轻举妄动
hold your position until he told otherwise.
我会开着视频
I will keep this feed open.
"朱玛将军表明
"general juma has demonstrated
即使像美国一样的暴政国家..."
"that even a tyrant state like the u.s..."
准备好
Be ready.
杰克  听我说
Jack, listen to me.
朱玛不是单独行动的
Juma's not solely coordinating this attack.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我听见了他用卫星电话
I heard him talking on his sat phone.
和外面的人里应外合
He's coordinating with someone on the outside.
他们给朱玛实时情报
They were giving him real-time intel.
你认为那些是白宫内部人员吗
You think it's someone in the white house?
我不知道
I don't know.
但是就算我们制服朱玛
But even if we take juma down,
总统还是处在危险之中
The president may still be in danger.
你是我知道的
You're the only one I know
唯一一个可以做这件事的人  杰克
Who can do this, jack.
查出朱玛的同党是谁
Find out who juma's working with.
莫斯探员  白宫西翼发生了爆炸
Agent moss, a device has been detonated in the west wing.
副总统阁下   白宫里发生了爆炸
Mr. vice president, there's been an explosion at the white house
-爆炸  -是的
An explosion? yes, sir.
总统那边的网络视频信号丢失
The president's internet feed has gone dark.
我们看到了  怎么回事
We saw that. what's happening?
不清楚  阁下
I don't know, sir,
我要下命令行动了  出发
But we're going in under my authority. let's go.
那不是你能决定的
That is not your decision.
全体注意  执行D计划
all teams, attack plan delta.
-莫斯探员  听我的指令  -十万火急
Agent moss, you're under orders! agent moss! code green.
冲  冲  冲
Go, go, go!
皮尔斯  保护总统
Pierce, get to the president!
总统阁下  您没事吧
Madam president, are you okay? mm-hmm.
我们必须马上离开这
We need get out of here right now.
你们都跟着我
Both of you, come with me.
我们走  这边
Let's go. this way.
总统阁下  身子放低
Madam president, get down.
等安全了再起身
Stay low till I know we're clear.
诺加兹
Ngozi...
杀了那些人质
Kill the hostages.
总统我来杀
The president is mine!
乌铎
Udo...
Udo?
不要  不要
No, no, no, no!
不许动
Don't move!
Don't you move!
安全
Clear.
我们安全了
We're clear!
特勤局  总统在这
Secret service! I have the president!
我是特勤局的亚伦·皮尔斯
Aaron pierce, secret service.
阁下  我们走
Let's go, ma'am.
总统阁下  这边
Madam president, this way!
总统在这
We have the president.
总统安全了
The president is secure!
重复  总统安全了
Repeat We have the president.
这边  阁下
This way, ma'am.
蕾妮  我们现在必须保护总统出去
Renee! we gotta get the president out of here now!
这边  阁下
This way, ma'am.
亲爱的  没事了
It's all right, darling.
一切都会好起来的
It's gonna be all right.
走  走  走
Move! move! move!
这边走
This way. this way.
总统阁下
Madam president...
我们仍在搜查白宫西翼
We're still sweeping the west wing.
但我们相信所有敌人均被击毙
But we do believe all the hostiles have been accounted for.
现在请您和您的女儿
Now you and your daughter
继续留在这  直到我们控制了这幢楼
Will stay here until we finish securing the building.
我知道
I understand.
一旦我们确定白宫安全
Now once we get the all clear,
我们会将您转移到安德鲁空军基地
We're going to move you to andrews air force base.
不  我就留在这
No, i'm staying right here.
阁下  这是为您的安全着想
Ma'am, it's your your own safety.
尽你所能保证白宫的安全
Do what's necessary to make sure this building safe
我是不会离开这的
Because I'm not going anywhere.
美国人民必须知道
The american people need to know
总统仍旧坐镇白宫
That the president is in the white house.
遵命  总统阁下
Yes, madam president.
我们牺牲了多少人
How many people did we lose?
还不知道
It's too early to tell.
医务组正在治疗伤员
Medical teams are on their way to treat the wounded.
我们会在白宫西翼设置一个急救点
We're going to set up a triage unit in the east wing.
好的
All right.
我要尽快和副总统通话
I'd like to speak To the vice president as soon as possible.
遵命  阁下
Yes, ma'am.
我还要尽快知道我的丈夫怎么样了
And i need to know how my husband's doing.
可以帮我联系一下在西阿林顿的
Would you please contact dr. lee schulman
李·舒尔曼医生吗
At west arlington hospital?
当然  总统阁下
Yes, madam president.
谢谢
Thank you.
皮尔斯探员怎么样了
How's agent pierce?
医生说他会没事的
They said he's gonna be okay.
你还好吗
What about you?
我不知道
I'm not sure.
我仍不能相信发生的一切
I still can't believe this happened.
我还以为他会把我们都杀光
I thought they were gonna kill all of us.
当时我太害怕了
I was so scared.
已经结束了
It's over...
我们安全了
And we're safe...
得感谢那些英勇无畏的人们
Thanks to a lot of brave people.
打扰一下  总统阁下
Excuse me, madam president,
副总统在安全线路上
The vice president is on a secure line.
我马上就来
I'll be right there.
你说要把以前不愉快的事忘掉
Did you mean what you said
是认真的吗
About putting the past behind us?
我当然是认真的
Of course i meant it.
我再也不想失去你了
I don't ever want to lose you again.
不会的
You won't.
总统安全了  杰克
The president's safe, jack.
她在总统官邸  很安全
She's in the residence. she's secure.
我很遗憾  杰克
I am so sorry, jack.
我知道他是你的好朋友
I know that he was your friend.
去死的本该是我
It was supposed to be me.
本该是我去引爆炸弹的
I was supposed to set off the explosion
让他保护总统
So that he could secure the president.
他为国家捐躯  死得其所
He died protecting his country.
是的
Yeah.
这次袭击还没完
This isn't over yet.
莫斯探员
Agent moss...
朱玛一伙不是单独在行动
Juma and his men were not working alone.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我和总统躲在安全屋的时候
When i was in the lockdown with the president,
比尔说  他听见朱玛在卫星电话上
Bill said he heard juma talking on a sat phone.
从外面的人那里获得实时情报
Said he was getting real-time intel From someone on the ouide.
-是谁  -我不知道
Who? i don't know.
重点是  袭击还没有结束
The point is, i don't think this threat is over,
我不认为总统已经安全了
And i don't think the president is safe.
你确定布坎南的情报可靠吗
You sure buchanan heard this right?
如果情报不可靠他是不会信口开河的
He wouldn't have told me unless he were sure.
现在唯一的线索就是莱恩·伯内特
And right now the only lead we've got is Ryan Burnett.
他知道这次袭击是在白宫
He knew about the attack
他很有可能知道
On the white house, and chances are,
和朱玛通话的人是何方神圣
He's gonna know who juma was talking to.
好吧  好吧  我会和他谈谈这件事的
All right, all right, i'll talk to him.
不  总统已准备赦免他了
No, the president already offered him immunity.
他拒绝了
He turned it down.
他什么都不会告诉你
He's not gonna tell you anything,
但我能令他开口
But he will talk to me.
为什么  你难道又要给他用刑吗
Why is that, jack, 'cause you tortured him?
我不需要碰他  只要让他放明白点
I don't need to touch him. i just need him to think
我是不会善罢甘休的
I'm there to finish what i started.
我向你保证
And i promise you
他会对我们和盘托出
He will tell us everything we need to know.
拉里  拜托了
Larry, please,
这是比尔死前最后的遗愿
The last thing bill asked for before he died
他希望我能战斗到底  这是我欠他的
Was for me to follow this through. I owe him that.
我向你保证
Look, i give you my word.
我不会动伯内特一根汗毛
I will not touch burnett.
杰克  听着  我理解你的朋友
Jack, look, i understand about your friend,
真的  但总统命令我羁押你
I do, but i got standing orders from the president to take you into custody.
我必须得带你回调查局
I gotta get you back to fbi,
但我保证会调查的  好吗
But i promise you i'll look into this, all right?
鲍威尔探员  给鲍尔戴上手铐
Agent powell, handcuff mr. bauer.
带他去2号集结地
Take him down to staging area b.
先生  请把双手放到脑后
Sir, put your hands on top of your head.
-拉里  -如果你只想说他是对的
- Larry...  - if you're gonna tell me he's right about this
我不想听
I don't want to hear it.
这就是问题所在
Yes, that's the problem. you're not
你根本听不进他说的话
listening to what he said
你能不能别为他辩护了
When are you gonna stop defending this guy?
我不是在维护他
I'm not defending him,
我是觉得他说的是对的
I'm defending a good idea.
我说了我会调查的
I just said i will look into this!
干你的活儿  把这栋楼封锁起来
Now do you job, finish locking down the building.
雷诺兹探员
Agent reynolds.
我要见总统  是紧急情况
I need to speak with the president. it's urgent.
她在安全地带
She's in a secure location.
你得找伊桑·卡宁
You'll need to go through ethan kanin.
-他在哪  -他刚到
- Where is he?  - he just arrived.
他在去见总统的路上
He's on his way to see the president.
多谢
Thanks.
总统和她女儿都在官邸中
The president's in the residence with her daughter.
检查过她们了
They've both been checked over
-她们都安然无恙  -感谢上帝
- And they're in good condition.  - thank god.
我要尽快会见秘书处
I want a conference with the sec staff
和参谋长联席会议成员
And the joint chiefs as soon as possible.
除了总统那  白宫其他地方的通讯
We're routing all white house
正在恢复中
communications except the president
我们还建立了个临时指挥所
And we're setting up a temporary command post.
好
Good.
卡宁先生  我有事找你
Mr. kanin, i need to speak with you.
我要去见总统
I'm on my way to see the president.
我知道  但事情特别紧急
Yes, i know, sir, but it's extremely urgent.
只要耽搁您一会
It'll only take a few moments.
好吧
All right.
怎么了  沃克探员
What is it, agent walker?
我们注意到一些新的情报
Some new intel has just come to our attention
需要立即做出反应
And we need to act on it immediately.
我想找总统  但被挡住了
I tried to reach the president, but i couldn't get through.
-愿闻其详  -长官  对总统的威胁
- I'm listening.  - sir, the threat to
还没完全解除
the president may not be over.
我们有理由相信  朱玛背后有人撑腰
We've reason to believe that general juma was not acting alone.
比尔·布坎南死前
Before bill buchanan died,
他看到朱玛和某人用卫星电话联络
He saw general juma communicating With someone on a sat phone.
现在  我们能确定
At this point, we can confirm
调查局探员刚进入白宫
That fbi agents entered the white house moments ago,
有报告称听到持续的枪声
And there were reports of sustained gunfire.
看上去当局已经控制了白宫西翼
It appears that authorities are now in control of the west wing,
我们还在等待调查局有关人质的消息
And we are expecting word from our fbi source Of the status of the hostages.
目前没有任何官方的消息
While there has been no official comment...
有什么消息
So what have we got?
总统还活着
The president's alive.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
我们同时监视着不同部门的服务器
We've been monitoring interagency servers.
消息传出来   朱玛死了  泰勒还活着
Word just went out. juma's dead, taylor survived.
你猜发生什么了
What happened do you think?
细节还不清楚
We don't know any details yet,
但我们会继续监视的
But we'll keep monitoring.
你得佩服下那婊子
Well... you gotta admire the damn bitch.
她不会轻言放弃
She doesn't give up easily.
对不起  长官  我们
I'm sorry, sir. we, uh,
没能完全控制局面
Just didn't have enough control over the situation.
格雷格  你看上去很紧张
Greg, you look tense.
帮帮忙
Do me a favor.
喝点酒  放松下
Have a drink, relax.
朱玛遵守了诺言
Juma held up his part of the bargain.
我们的目的都达到了
We're getting what we wanted.
就我而言  一切还尽在掌握
As far as i'm concerned, everything's still on track.
武器在哪了
Where are the weapons now?
几个小时后我们就可以卸货了
A shipment should ready for pickup in the next couple of hours.
好  给查普曼打电话
Good. get chapman on the phone.
我想确定几个目标
I want to nail down some targets.
长官  你要的直升机已经过来了
Sir, the chopper you requested is on its way.
10分钟内到
It'll be here in ten minutes.
你们要护送鲍尔回调查局
You'll be escorting Mr Bauer back to the FBI.
把他关在指挥中心
Hold him in the command center.
遵命  长官
Yes, sir.
我是拉里 ·莫斯
This is larry moss.
我是伊桑·卡宁  我听说
This is ethan kanin. i understand
你要把杰克·鲍尔押回调查局
You're taking jack bauer back to fbi?
是的  长官  他将被审讯
Yes, sir. he's gonna be debriefed
并被遣送回联邦调查局候审
And remanded into federal custody.
我希望你能暂缓执行
I want you to put that on hold.
怎么了
Sir?
我刚和沃克探员谈过
I just spoke with agent walker.
她告诉我朱玛可能和别人
She told me juma may have been working with someone
暗中勾结  而且有可能
On the outside, and that there may be
还有对总统的其他威胁
An ongoing threat to the president.
是的
Yes, that's true.
我希望你能让杰克·鲍尔
I want you to send jack bauer
去审讯莱恩·伯内特
to question ryan burnett.
莫斯探员
Agent moss?
长官  我觉得那样不好
Sir, i think that's a mistake.
沃克探员和我说了你的顾忌
Yes, agent walker shared your concerns with me,
我也经过了深思熟虑
And i've given this some thought.
如果伯内特确实知道朱玛的同伙是谁
If burnett does know who juma was working with,
鲍尔的手段可能会是
Bauer's approach may be our best
得到情报的最好机会
chance to get that information
恕我直言  长官  鲍尔差点杀了他
With respect, sir, bauer almost killed this man.
我当时在现场  莫斯探员
I was there, agent moss,
但这次审讯是可以控制的
But this will be a controlled interrogation.
我们利用伯内特对鲍尔的恐惧心理
We're gonna play on burnett's fears.
鲍尔只要单独现身
Bauer's presence alone should be enough
就足够让他开口了
To intimidate him into talking.
长官  鲍尔是个不确定因素
Sir, bauer is a wild card.
他进屋见到伯内特之后
We have no idea what he'll do
不知道他会做出什么来
When he gets in that room with burnett.
我考虑到这事会有风险
I realize there's a risk.
所以此事得由我全权负责
That's why you're going to do this under my authority And my authority alone.
你不和总统说这事吗
You're not taking this to the president?
不  如有意外
No. if something does go wrong,
我希望总统不受牵连
I want to make sure the president is protected.
恕我直言  我觉得你不告诉总统
With respect, sir, i think you're not telling the president
是因为你知道她决不会批准
'cause you know she'd never allow this.
你的异议我清楚了  莫斯探员
You've made your objections clear, agent moss.
我们不要再争论此事了
I'm not going to debate this with you.
我让你带鲍尔去审讯伯内特
I want you to take bauer to question burnett.
这是命令  你明白吗
That's a direct order. do you understand?
明白
I understand.
我希望你能对此次审讯全程监控
And i'm counting on you to supervise every second of that interrogation.
我期待事成之后  你能有份完整报告
I'll expect a full report as soon as you're done.
好的  长官
Yes, sir.
我希望能够亲自和死者家属谈话
I want to speak personally to the families of everyone we lost tonight, so...
通知到他们后和我说一声
Keep me informed as they're notified.
没问题  总统阁下
Absolutely, madam president.
安吉拉·纳尔逊到的时候
And the minute angela nelson
直接带她来见我
Gets here, send her straight up to me.
需要准备对全国民众的讲话稿
We need to start working on the speech to the country.
当然  总统阁下
Of course, madam president.
帕特里克
Patrick,
你刚经历了一场严酷的考验
You have just been through a terrible ordeal.
你确定没事吗
Are you sure you're okay?
我没事的
I'll be fine.
这事对专心工作有帮助
It helps to focus on work.
我理解
I understand.
谢谢你  帕特里克
Thank you, patrick.
感谢上帝你没事
Thank god you're all right.
你感觉如何
How you feeling?
仿佛刚从噩梦中醒来
Like i just woke up from a nightmare.
真难以置信  伊桑
It was unbelievable, ethan.
确实不堪回想  奥利维亚还好吗
I can't even imagine it. how's olivia?
她被吓到了  但会好起来的
She's shaken up, but she's going to be okay.
听到这我很欣慰
I'm glad to hear it.
伊桑  今晚我们牺牲了很多好战友
We lost some good people tonight, ethan.
要竭尽所能多方寻求帮手
We're going to need all the help we can get.
我考虑让奥利维亚加入进来
I'm thinking about bringing olivia on
担任特别顾问
As a special advisor.
总统阁下
Madam president,
经过此次事件  您不愿与女儿分开
I can understand your not wanting to be separated
这我能理解
From your daughter after what's happened.
正是因为发生了这次事件
Especially after what's happened,
我们需要有能力的人加入
We need people who can do the job.
我对奥利维亚的能力无可置疑
I'm not disputing olivia's competence,
但她也是个政治负担
but she's also a political Liability.
大选时她的所为大家都还历历在目
Nobody's forgotten what she did during the campaign,
她对媒体散布谣言
Leaking damaging personal information
诽谤您的竞选对手
About your opponent to the press.
奥利维亚知错了
Olivia knows what she did was wrong.
她差点毁掉您的竞选
She almost cost you the election.
她已经变了
She's changed.
伊桑  我们有谈过此事
We talked about it, ethan,
她也表示自己将负全责
And she is accepting full responsibility.
她已经吸取教训了
She has learned from her mistakes.
我希望忘掉过去的种种  放眼未来
I'm willing to put the past behind us so we can move ahead.
我还是认为此事不妥
I still think it's a mistake.
我不在乎你怎么认为
I don't care what you think!
抱歉 伊桑
I am so sorry, ethan.
你知道我也不想这样
You know i don't mean that.
但我意已决
But i've made up my mind.
我要奥利维亚加入我的幕僚之中
I want olivia to join my administration.
并且我希望由你来发起
And i want it to come from you.
我
Me?
由你亲自任命她职务
Your offering her this position
能有助于你们俩化干戈为玉帛
Would be a good way to extend an olive branch.
我要你们俩相安无事
I need the two of you to make peace.
遵命  总统阁下
All right, madam president.
我会和她谈的
I'll talk to her.
谢谢你  伊桑
Thank you, ethan.
我听说沃克探员之前找我
I understand agent walker was trying to reach me.
对  我联系了她
That's right, but i spoke to her.
她有何事
What did she want?
这是一些琐碎公事  总统阁下
Just some procedural matters, madam president.
我已处理了
I took care of it.
拉里  你找我吗
Larry, you wanted to see me?
我刚接到伊桑·卡宁的电话
I just got off the phone with ethan kanin.
听着  我不想背着你做事
Look, i didn't want to go behind your back,
但是是你让我没有选择余地的
But you didn't leave me any choice.
我不给你留余地吗
I didn't leave you a...?
你怎么就不能选择服从命令听指挥呢
How about you choose to follow orders?
我很抱歉  拉里
I'm sorry, larry.
不  我觉得你不会
No. i don't think you are.
拉里  今天我亲眼目睹了杰克的作为
Larry, i've seen jack do some terrible things today.
粗暴之极  我仍不敢苟同
Things that i still can't justify.
但结果却每次都证明他是对的
But he has been right every time.
知道吗  我不禁在想
And you know what? i can't help but think
如果我们能让他放手去干
That maybe if we had just stayed out of his way,
或许这些悲剧都不会发生
None of this would have happened.
听着  我很抱歉
Look, i am sorry
不该背着你做事
That i went behind your back,
但我向你保证  伯内特的处置方式
But i... i promise you this play with burnett
一定得按杰克的意思办
Will go down just the way jack says.
如果你觉得自己和杰克一条战线
If you think you're going with bauer,
那你一定是疯了
You are out of your mind.
就算你有能耐
You may have gotten
让白宫发令  可我仍是行动指挥
A white house order, but i'm still running this operation.
我会带杰克去见伯内特
I'll take bauer to see Burnett.
你回调查局
You're going back to fbi.
我会把你扫地出门
I want you to clean out your office
并收回你的联邦探员徽章
And hand in your badge.
我要将你无限期停职
I'm suspending you indefinitely.
好吧  我知道你很不爽  但事情还没完
Okay. i know that you're upset larry, but this isn't over.
你仍然需要我
You're going to need me.
我需要的是能让我信任的人
What i need are people that i can trust.
我原以为你就是
I thought that was you.
听好了  你别以为自己得偿所愿了
Look, you may think you got what you wanted,
让蕾妮背着我行事
Getting renee to go behind my back,
但伊桑命令我  让你去审问伯内特
But ethan kanin ordered me to let you question burnett.
你审问时  我都会全程死死盯住你
I'm going to be watching you every second you're in there.
你胆敢让我不爽  你就死定了
You do one thing i don't like, you're finished.
-听懂了吗  -明白
You understand me? understood.
你不该因此牵连蕾妮
You should leave renee out of this.
她也只是做自己认为对的事情
She was just doing what she thought was right.
是吗  她可能会因此丢了饭碗
Yeah? well, she may lose her job over it.
她是你手下最棒的探员
She's the best agent you've got.
她无视我的权威
She circumvented my authority.
对此我不能置之不理
I can't just ignore that.
我认识她9年了
I've known this woman for nine years,
从未见过她做事会像
And i've never seen her do the kind of things she's done
过去9小时所做的那样
In the last nine hours.
我们已将目标缩小到 12个东部沿海城市
We've narrowed the list down To 12 targets along the eastern seaboard.
都在发射基地300公里半径范围以内
They're all within 300 kilometers of the base.
有多少人
How many people?
每个目标区大概1至1.5万人
10,000 to 15,000 in each target zone.
死亡率估计会是多少
And our kill ratio would be what?
我们选择的城市
Well, we've chosen these areas
都是人口密度最高的
for maximum population density
按此估算估计高达80%
So the ratio could be as high as 80%.
希望我们永远都不必真去确证这个结果
Let's hope we never have to find out.
把这些坐标传到战术行动组去
Get these coordinates down to the boys in tac-ops.
-让他们运作起来  -遵命  长官
Have them start programming them in. Yes, sir.
我们刚拦截到调查局的一条信息
We just intercepted a flash memo from the fbi.
杰克·鲍尔正在去肯尼迪纪念医院的路上
Jack bauer is on his way to kennedy memorial hospital
准备去审问伯内特
To question burnett.
鲍尔已被拘捕了  怎么可能还去审问
Bauer was arrested. how is this possible?
白宫下达了总统行政命令
There was an executive order from the white house
让鲍尔有权审问伯内特
Giving bauer access to burnett.
鲍尔是不到黄河心不死的
Bauer will finish what he started.
伯内特早晚会和盘托出
Burnett will tell him everything.
不  长官  他不会的
No, he won't, sir.
我已派人去医院干掉伯内特
I have already sent somebody to the hospital to deal with burnett.
到时候将一并干掉鲍尔
He can take care of bauer at the same time.
你派谁去的
Who did you send?
奎恩
Quinn.
奎恩身手不错
Oh. quinn's good.
鲍尔也不好对付
Bauer's good, too.
莫斯探员  我们已经封锁了整个楼层
Agent moss, we've locked down the entire floor.
在伯内特房间
We equipped burnett's room
我们安装了两组监视器和窃听器
With two cameras and audio surveillance.
他在哪
Where is he?
大厅尽头
Down the hall.
稍等一会
It's going to be a moment.
大夫要让他苏醒过来
Doctor has to revive him.
为什么  发生什么事了
Why? what happened?
我们给他注射了强效镇定剂
He was given a heavy sedative.
刚到时他情况很糟糕
He was in pretty bad shape when he got here.
温顿大夫  联邦探员拉里·莫斯
Dr. wyndam, special agent Larry moss,
杰克·鲍尔
jack bauer.
我知道你们到这
I understand youe here
-是要审问我的病人  -没错
To interrogate my patient. that's right.
上次审问后  目前他仍处在恢复状态
Well, he's still recovering from his last Interrogation,
所以  如果你们又要来虐待他
so if you're here to brutalize him again,
-我是不会参与的  -大夫  您的病人
I won't be party to it. doctor, your patient
涉嫌参与袭击白宫的恐怖活动
Was involved in a terrorist attack against the white house
企图谋杀美国总统
In an effort to kill the president of the united states,
我相信他的同伙
And i believe the people he's working with
正企图卷土重来  如果您对此有意见...
Want to try it again, so if you've got a problem...
我们不会伤害他的  大夫
We won't harm him, doctor.
审讯都在可控范围进行  拜托了
This will be a controlled interrogation. please,
请你配合我们
We need your cooperation.
他还需要几分钟才能醒过来
It's going to take him a couple of minutes to come out of it
你是谁
Who are you?
嘘  一个朋友
Shh. i'm a friend.
你叫什么
What's your name?
罗伯特
Robert.
-罗伯特吗  -对
Robert? yeah.
你心脏手术后还在康复阶段吗
You're recovering from heart surgery?
是的
Yeah.
你有妻子吗  罗伯特
Do you have a wife, robert?
没有  她过世了
No. she passed away.
孩子呢  孙子呢
Children? grandchildren?
没有
No.
这位呢
What about this man?
他有家人吗
Does he have family?
有
Yeah.
子孙满堂
Lots of grandkids.
来探望他的时候  吵死人了
Make a hell of a noise when they visit.
-胳膊怎么样了  -再过几小时
- How's your arm? - I should be back
就没事了
on my feet in a couple of hours
你呢  女士
And you, ma'am?
我没事  吃点阿司匹林就得了
Oh, it's nothing a little aspirin won't take care of.
谢谢你的救命之恩
I want to thank you for what you did.
你为我挡了一枪  救了我一命
You took a bullet for me. you saved my life.
这是我应该做的  女士
There is no need to thank me, ma'am.
也对  你只是尽职尽责罢了
Right, you were just doing your job.
只不过  这一回
Only in this case,
你4年前就退休了
It wasn't really your job since you retired
这就不再是你的职责了
Four years ago.
是的  女士  这倒是真的
Yes, ma'am, that's true.
能告诉我为什么退休吗
Do you mind if i ask you why?
跟玛撒·洛根有关系吗
Did it have to do with martha logan?
我和玛撒...曾经是好朋友
Martha and i were... close.
发生在她身上的一切  对你打击肯定不小
It must have been hard for you-- what happened to her.
往事不堪回事啊
I'd prefer not to talk about it.
对不起
I'm sorry.
没必要道歉
You don't have to apologize.
把我当朋友吧  皮尔斯探员
I hope you won't be a stranger, agent pierce.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你
And, uh...
可以叫我亚伦
It's aaron.
好的  亚伦
Okay, aaron.
你好好休息吧
You get some rest.
如果可以的话
I'd like to head back to the residence now
我想打道回府了
If that's okay?
奥利维亚
Olivia...
我正找你呢
I was just coming to see you.
你没事太好了
I'm glad you're all right.
谢谢
Thank you.
有时间说两句话吗
You have a moment to talk?
当然
Sure.
坦率地说
The blunt fact of the matter is...
政府遭受了巨大的损失
This administration has just suffered some terrible losses,
我们需要你的帮助
And we need help.
总统和我想让你加入内阁
The president and i would like you to consider coming on board
担任总统的特别顾问
As special advisor to the president.
我
I, uh...
不得不承认  我有点吃惊
I have to say i'm a little surprised.
-吃惊  -我是说  竟是你正式批准的
- Surprised? - oh, that you'd sign off on this.
你妈妈说已决定冰释前嫌
You mother said she's ready to put the past behind her...
我也会这么做
And so am i.
竞选的时候  我做事过于激进
I overstepped my bounds in the campaign
我大错特错了
and i was wrong.
你能认识到这点  太好了
I'm glad you see it that way.
但是让我困扰的不是过去  伊桑
But it's not the past that concerns me, ethan.
而是现在发生的一切
It's what's happening right now,
是从我妈妈接管政府以后  发生的一切
And what's been happening ever since my mother took office.
你什么意思
Excuse me?
如果有个称职的首席顾问
Do you think any of this would have happened
你觉得这一切的一切
If my mother had a chief advisor
还会发生吗
Who knew what the hell was going on in her administration?
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
整个政府上下都被腐化了
Her government was corrupted on every level,
而这一切居然就在你的眼皮底下发生
And it all happened right under your nose.
即使你自己也觉得这种失败让你良心不安
Even you have to admit, it's an unconscionable failure on your part.
坦白地说
Frankly, i'm surprised
我不明白为什么你还不辞职
You haven't tendered your resignation.
你这样对我说话太放肆了
You have no right to speak to me that way.
说话要实事求是
You don't know what you're talking about.
你有证据吗
You don't have the facts.
我正要找证据呢
I intend to get the facts.
我会找出是谁辜负了我妈妈
I'm going to find out exactly who failed my mother,
我会确保让他再也坐不回原来的位置
And i am going to make sure that that person never is in a position to do it again.
失陪
Excuse me.
好  进去吧
Okay, let's go.
我会在这盯着你的
I'll be watching.
你动他一根汗毛  就别想再继续了
You lay one finger on him, it's over.
好
Right.
他恢复知觉了
He's coming around.
很好
Good.
醒醒
Wake up.
还记得我吗
Remember me?
天哪
Oh, my god.
你来这干嘛
What the hell are you doing here?
我刚从白宫赶过来啊
I've just come from the white house.
朱玛的阴谋破产了
Juma's attack failed.
他跟他的同党都死翘翘了
He's dead, and so are his men.
今天死了好多无辜的人
A lot of innocent people died today.
都是好人
Good people.
包括我的一个朋友  比尔·布坎南
Including a friend of mine-- bill buchanan.
你见过他吧
You might have met him.
你离我远点
You stay the hell away from me.
给我叫律师来
And i want to talk to a lawyer right now.
你听见没  我要见律师
Do you hear me? i want to talk to a lawyer!
来人啊  救我
Somebody get me the hell out of here!
你哪也去不成了
You're not going anywhere.
这就你跟我了  哥们
It's just you and me, pal.
你还真以为你能躲得过去啊
Did you really think you were going to get away with it?
来人啊  救我
Somebody please, help me!
别白费唇舌了  没人来救你
You're wasting your breath. they're not coming for you.
别打我  我全招
Please don't hurt me. i'll tell you anything you want.
你们听见没  我愿意全招
Do you hear that-- i'm ready to talk.
你们想知道什么
I'll tell you anything
我都告诉你们  请别把他跟我关一起
You want to know! just get him out of here!
-我全都招  -他们懒得理你了
- I'm ready to talk! - They're done talking to you.
所以才叫我来
That's why they sent me.
你不能这么做  你无权这么做
Please, you can't do this! you have no right!
这样做违法
This isn't legal!
怎么回事
What happened?
不清楚
I don't know.
好像接收不到音频了
Looks like we lost the sound feed.
给我点时间
Give me a second.
还跟你讲什么法律  伯内特先生
There are no laws in here, mr. burnett.
你助纣为虐
You aided and abetd terrorists,
差点害死了美国总统
Who then tried to kill the president of the united states.
你该得到你应有的惩罚了
Now you have to answer for that.
法律在你这  已经不适用了
The rules don't apply to you anymore.
不  不要  你们不能让他动我
No, please, please, you can't let him touch me!
-不要  不要让他动我  -闭嘴
- Please, you can't let him do this...! - shut up!
中继线可能有点小故障
It could be a glitch in the trunk line.
-该死  快修啊  -我修着呢  长官
- Damn it, fix the thing! - i'm trying, sir.
鲍尔
Bauer?
他破坏了电子锁
He jammed the electronic bolt.
-还有别的路可以进去吗  -没有
- Is there another way in? - no.
杰克
Jack...
该死  鲍尔  给我开门
Damn it, bauer, open the door!
让保安封锁整个医院
Have security lock down the hospital.
发出全面缉捕通告  全力捉拿杰克·鲍尔
I want a high-priority APB issued for jack bauer.
包括所有部门
All agencies.
-完事了 -很好  谢谢
- t's done. Good. - thank you.
成了
It's done.
伯内特死了
Burnett's dead.
鲍尔呢
And bauer?
栽赃给他了
They'll think he killed burnett.
这样便神不知鬼不觉了
So, nobody will know That we were involved.
妙计
Good.
那当然
Yeah.
这下我们可以看笑话了
Now we're having some fun.
我是莫斯
Agent moss.
拉里  我是杰克  听我说
Larry, it's jack. listen to me.
你在哪
Where are you?
我没有杀伯内特
I didn't kill burnett.
-我是被陷害的  -陷害
- i'm being set up. - set up?
有人在屋里释放了神经毒气
A man released some kind of nerve agent into the room.
让我动弹不得
It immobilized me.
他从天花板上下来  杀了伯内特
He came through the ceiling and killed burnett.
我发誓我没说谎  我看着他这么做的
I swear to you, i'm not lying. i watched him do it.
你马上回来  我们再想办法
Get back in here, we'll work this out.
你知道我不能回去的
I can't, you know that.
如果你是清白的  你就可以回来
you can if you're innocent.
他们这样陷害我  而不杀我
Look, there is a reason why they
其中定有隐情
wanted me framed and didn't kill me
这样就能利用我来让你分心
They're trying to keep you distracted by dealing with me
他们好趁机继续不可告人的秘密
So they can finish what they started.
别让他们侥幸成功
Don't let them get away with this.
恐怖袭击还没有结束
This threat is not over.
杰克
Jack...
Jack?!
该死
Damn it!